=Demon Emperor's Little Matchmaker=
= صانع الثقاب الصغير للإمبراطور الشيطاني =
=Episode 27=
= الحلقة 27 =
The forbidden skill on Young Master is neutralized.
يتم تحييد المهارة المحظورة على السيد الصغير.
He's now worthy of the name of
إنه الآن يستحق اسم
Demon Emperor.
شيطان الإمبراطور.
Congratulations, Wuyou.
مبروك يا وويو.
Let me do it.
دعني افعلها.
Hubby, we just got married,
بعل ، لقد تزوجنا للتو ،
yet you've to attend the Demon Realm Conference.
ومع ذلك ، يجب عليك حضور مؤتمر عالم الشياطين.
The marriage leave of Demon Realm is too short.
إجازة زواج عالم الشياطين قصيرة جدًا.
Why don't I just stay?
لماذا لا أبقى فقط؟
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
This is the best chance for you to be famous
هذه أفضل فرصة لكي تصبح مشهوراً
after being recognized by the Demon Realm.
بعد أن تم التعرف عليه من قبل عالم الشياطين.
How can I delay it?
كيف يمكنني تأخيره؟
Don't worry. I promise that
لا تقلق.  أعدك بذلك
I'll get back as soon as I'm done.
سأعود حالما انتهيت.
Okay.
تمام.
I warn you.
احذرك.
Take good care of your sister-in-law.
اعتن بأخت زوجتك جيدًا.
If she misses any of her fingers,
إذا فقدت أي من أصابعها ،
I'll not have mercy on you.
لن ارحمك.
Wuyou, don't worry.
Wuyou ، لا تقلق.
Leave your wife to me.
اترك زوجتك لي.
I'll leave my wife to you.
سأترك لك زوجتي.
The two of us...
نحن الإثنان...
Give it to me. Hurry.
اعطني اياه.  عجل.
Young Master, I'll wait for you in front.
سيد الشباب ، سأنتظرك في المقدمة.
Honey, wait.
عزيزتي ، انتظري.
I'm not done.
لم انتهي بعد.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Sir.
سيد.
Move aside.
تحرك جانبا.
Get your face away from me.
ابعد وجهك عني
Sir.
سيد.
This is the best chance to catch them.
هذه أفضل فرصة للقبض عليهم.
As long as we have Qiao Chuchu,
طالما لدينا Qiao Chuchu ،
no matter how strong Li Wuyou is,
بغض النظر عن مدى قوة Li Wuyou ،
he can only surrender.
يمكنه فقط الاستسلام.
Listen. Chin up.
استمع.  اعلى الذقن.
Not even a single fly is allowed in.
ولا يُسمح بدخول ذبابة واحدة.
Yes, Your Highness.
نعم سموكم.
Mother, why are you?
امي لماذا انت
Greetings, Your Majesty.
تحياتي جلالة الملك.
Wuming.
ويومينغ.
I came to send you some dumplings.
جئت لأرسل لك بعض الزلابية.
But there was a shadow
لكن كان هناك ظل
that went that way.
ذهب بهذه الطريقة.
What? Where?
ماذا؟  أين؟
Right over there.
هناك.
What is that?
ما هذا؟
No. It's Yaksha. Come with me.
رقم انها ياقشا.  تعال معي.
Pursue!
لاحق!
Stop!
قف!
Hurry!
عجل!
It's boring to sleep alone.
من الممل أن تنام بمفردك.
I miss Li Wuyou.
افتقد لي وويو.
Li Wuyou smells better.
رائحة Li Wuyou أفضل.
Who is that?
من ذاك؟
It's me.
هذا أنا.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Chuchu.
حلمات.
Just now Wuming and the rest saw
فقط الآن Wuming ورأى الباقي
that someone unknown was breaking in.
أن شخصًا غير معروف كان يقتحم.
I was worried that you might be in danger.
كنت قلقة من أن تكون في خطر.
So I came to check you out.
لذلك أتيت لأفحصك.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Your Majesty will never be so nice to me.
جلالة الملك لن يكون لطيفًا معي أبدًا.
Speak up.
تكلم.
What a smart young lady.
يا لها من شابة ذكية.
You're indeed someone from Matchmaker's Hall.
أنت بالفعل شخص من قاعة Matchmaker.
You're a demon.
أنت شيطان.
♪The wind of the early summer♪
رياح أوائل الصيف ♪
♪Created a starry sky♪
♪ خلق السماء المرصعة بالنجوم
♪The dream in my heart♪
الحلم في قلبي ♪
♪Froze at the street intersection in the morning♪
تجمد عند تقاطع الشارع صباحا
♪I've passed the end of the galaxy♪
♪ لقد اجتزت نهاية المجرة
♪I've seen the crowded traffic♪
♪ لقد رأيت ازدحام المرور ♪
♪In my mind♪
♪ في ذهني ♪
♪Your smile is engraved♪
♪ ابتسامتك محفورة ♪